mmaprofighter.com 2011-06-26

# Privacy & Security | Digital Chocolate

### Your Privacy Matters to Us

Welcome to Digital Chocolate, Inc. (”Digital Chocolate”). Your privacy is important to us. We have created this policy, which explains what personally identifiable information we collect from you on our Web sites such as but not limited to [http://www.digitalchocolate.com](http://www.digitalchocolate.com/) (the “Site”) and the games and forums we provide on various other websites (the Site and the games and forums collectively the “Services”. We reserve the right to change this policy at any time. If we decide to change this policy, we will post those changes on this page and update the date at the top of the page. The changes will be effective when posted, and your continued use of the Services after the effective date of such change constitutes your consent to the collection practices described in such revised statement. Please check this page on a regular basis and whenever you use the Services so that you remain aware of what information we collect and how we use it.

**What Information We Collect and How We Use It**  
When we use the term “personal information” in this policy, we are referring to personally identifiable information that specifically identifies an individual (such as an individual’s first and last name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card or other account number), and information about that individual or such individual’s activities or preferences when such information is directly linked to personally identifying information. __ Personal information does not include “aggregate” information, which is data we collect about the use of the Services or categories of Service users, from which any personal information has been removed. For example, information that forty-seven percent of the Services’ registered users identify themselves as male, but without identifying any specific individuals as male, is aggregate information. We collect aggregate data for a number of purposes, including to help us understand trends and user needs so that we can better consider new publications, products and services, and tailor existing publications, products and services to user desires. This policy in no way limits or restricts our collection of aggregate information.

### Automatically Collected Information

**Log files**  
When you visit our Site, Digital Chocolate collects standard information about your computer, such as your IP address, browser type and operating system version. We use this information to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Site, and to improve our products and services. This information may also be used to gather broad demographic information that does not personally identify you.

**Mobile applications**  
When you use some of our mobile applications, your wireless device may transmit information about your activities in the application as well as information you enter in the application, to our servers. We use this information to provide the service to you, to improve our applications and related services, and to gather broad demographic information that does not personally identify you. We may also use the information to learn about and resolve problems with the application, to improve the application and our other products and services, and to develop new products or services. In addition, if any application includes any location-based services, your location may be shared with Digital Chocolate while using such feature.

### Information You Provide to Us

At several places on our Services, we may collect certain information you provide to us which may contain personal information. The following are some examples of certain activities on the Services through which you may provide personal information.

**Registration**  
We may collect personal information when you register with us, either through the Site or one of the Services. Registration may require you to provide personal information, such as your name, mobile telephone number, an email address, a member name, and/or a PIN or password that will either be chosen by you or created for you by Digital Chocolate, credit card or other billing information and home and business postal address.  Additionally, we may also collect other types of information (known as demographic information) such as your date of birth, gender, hobbies, occupation, resume, company info, or computer or game related information. This demographic information may be associated with your personal information. Date of birth may be used to ensure compliance with applicable laws (together, these are your “Account Information”). We use this information to identify and communicate with you, such as in ratings, rankings, contests, special promotions and other activities in which you participate. Your member name may be viewable in communications with other members of the Services, so you should choose a member name that you are comfortable having displayed publicly.

**Contests, surveys and other activities**  
Digital Chocolate may also collect personal information, such as your name, address, telephone number, demographic information and information about your tastes and preferences that you provide when you enter a contest or sweepstakes or participate in a survey or similar activity on our Services. Additionally, you may be required to provide other personal information if you are selected as a winner in a contest or drawing.

**Interactive Features**  
Personal information may also be collected if you provide personal information in connection with interactive features of the Services, such as creating a profile, sending a wallpaper image to your phone, participating in discussions, leaving comments or inviting a friend. Additionally, information, such as your performance or rank in games or applications, or your friends’ member names, may be associated with your member name and displayed on our Services.

When you participate in interactive areas of the Services, certain information you post in connection with such application or on the Services is shared with other users, and your use of the Services constitutes your consent to share this information. For example, personal information that you post in any comments, reviews, profiles, discussion groups or other interactive area, or other information that is provided for the purpose of being shared is publicly available to other users and can potentially be viewed by anyone.

**Mobile Applications**  
Some of our mobile applications may require you to input your wireless telephone number or other personal information into the application. We use this information in connection with providing the application, such as to authenticate you and to communicate with you regarding our services by SMS, text message or other electronic means to your mobile device.

**Social games**

When you use any applications created by Digital Chocolate and that are available through social networking sites such as Facebook, we may record information regarding the use of that application, and we may collect other information that is visible on your social network page in accordance with the relevant terms of use of that social networking site.

It is your responsibility to read and accept the terms of the relevant social networking site.

**Subscriptions, resumes and other requests.**  
If you subscribe to the Digital Chocolate e-mail newsletter, request support, send us an email, submit a job application or resume or otherwise contact us through the Services, we collect personal information such as your name and email address and any other personal information you provide in such communication. We use such information that we collect in these manners to fulfill and contact you regarding your request and for the other purposes set forth in this policy.

### Other Use of Personal Information

When you register through the Services and submit your personal information to create a profile webpage or join one of the Services, the other users of the Services may see your username and the other information about you. We may display your personal information in your profile page and elsewhere on the Services according to your preference you set in your account. Any information you choose to provide should reflect how much you want other users of the Services to know about you. We recommend that you guard your anonymity and sensitive information and we encourage members to think carefully about what information about themselves they disclose in their profile pages. You can review and revise your profile information at any time. We recommend that you guard your anonymity and sensitive information and that you not use your real name as your username, since that would allow others to identify you.

In addition to the specific uses mentioned above, we may use the personal information we collect (a) to contact you about your use of the Services, such as for administrative purposes or to provide you with customer service; (b) for the purpose for which it was provided, such as to provide our products and Services, to fulfill or respond to your requests, to process transactions, and to send you the communications you requested; (c) to notify you about important changes to our policies or Services, (d) to contact you regarding new and existing Digital Chocolate features, products and Services, and special Digital Chocolate offers, promotions and events that we think you may find interesting and for other internal marketing, informational, product development and promotional purposes; (e) to request feedback and to improve the Services and our product and service offerings, and develop new products and services; (f) to provide product support;

### How to Update Your Personal Information and Contact Preferences

If you wish to stop receiving marketing communications from us, you can always opt out by replying to a message that we send you by clicking unsubscribe link located on the bottom of the e-mail.

## Changing or Deleting Your Information

All users may review, update, correct or delete the personal information in their registration profile by changing the applicable information in their account settings or, for Services that are hosted on a social networking site, by changing the applicable information in their profile page. If you completely delete all such information, then your account may become deactivated. If you would like us to delete your record in our system, please contact us and we will attempt to accommodate your request if we do not have any legal obligation to retain the record. See below for privacy contact information.

## Phishing

Identity theft and the practice currently known as “phishing” are of great concern to Digital Chocolate. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is a top priority. We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, your account ID, login password, or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication. For more information about phishing, visit the Federal Trade Commission’s website.

### How We Protect Your Information

We have put reasonable security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, destruction and alteration of information under our control. For example, when you access your Account Information, we use the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol to encrypt information you input before it is sent to us.

### Our Disclosure of Personal Information

Except as described in this policy, Digital Chocolate will not share your personal information with third parties unless you have consented to the disclosure or Digital Chocolate believes the disclosure is appropriate to (1) comply with the law or with legal process, (2) protect and defend our rights and property, such as to determine, bill and collect for amounts owed to us, (3) protect our customers or users, including from misuse or unauthorized use of the Digital Chocolate Services, or (4) protect the safety or property of our employees, customers, users or others. Digital Chocolate may disclose or transfer your personal information (1) to its corporate affiliates (for example, its subsidiaries or parent corporation), (2) to its service providers (like fulfillment, hosting, or payment service providers), but only for their use to provide the requested service, (3) to an acquirer in connection with the sale or other transfer of the business or assets of Digital Chocolate, or (4) where you provide your express consent to the disclosure. Digital Chocolate will require its corporate affiliates and service providers that receive your personal information to limit their use and disclosure of your information to the purposes for which you provided it.

Digital Chocolate may collect and create or derive aggregate statistics about our customers and visitors, as well as information regarding sales, traffic patterns, and related Service information that cannot be used to identify you. We may use this “aggregate” or “de-identified” information for various purposes, and may disclose it to third parties for example for industry analyses and demographic profiling and to deliver targeted advertising about other products and services.

### Links to Other Web Sites

Our Services may contain links to sites operated by third parties that we think may be of interest to you. If you choose to visit an advertiser by clicking on a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s website, and in such case you leave our Site, and our policies, including this privacy policy, no longer govern. Any information you provide to these third parties is subject to their privacy policies, which may differ from ours. Digital Chocolate is not responsible for the actions of those parties, the content of their Web sites and/or services, use of information you provide to them, or any products or services they may offer. Our link to a third-party site does not constitute our sponsorship of, or affiliation with, the third party. We encourage you to review and understand the privacy policies of these third parties before providing personal information to them.

### Cookies

The Digital Chocolate Web site uses “cookies,” which are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information and are used to either identify you as a returning customer or improve the experience on our Services. Third parties that place advertising banners or other content on our Services may also use cookies. Digital Chocolate is not responsible for the information collected by these third parties’ cookies or those third parties’ use of the information they collect.

Digital Chocolate uses “Clear GIFs” to analyze traffic on the Digital Chocolate Sites, and within HTML e-mails to determine whether the e-mails have been opened. Clear GIFs (also called Web Beacons, or Web Bugs) are small images embedded on web-pages and in email communications. Digital Chocolate does not use clear GIFS to collect or store any of your personal information.

### A Note About Children

At Digital Chocolate, we understand that children’s privacy is important. Our Services are not intended for use by children aged 12 or younger, and we do not intend to collect any personally identifiable information from children aged 12 or younger. If you are 12 years old or younger, do not submit any personal information to Digital Chocolate.

### How to Contact Us

Digital Chocolate welcomes your questions and comments about privacy. Please give us your feedback via email to [support@digitalchocolate.com](mailto:support@digitalchocolate.com).

(updated 3/19/2010)
